DANIELLE CARRINGTON, M.S.

Operations Manager / Big Data Analyst

469.243.0070 @ danielle.promo.mgr@gmail.com

② linkedin.com/in/danielle-carrington-ms-89163929/
♥ Frisco, TX

SUMMARY

Operations Manager with 10yrs of Project Management, proficient in broad based modeling, data processing, and data mining. Capable of creating, developing, testing, and deploying highly adaptive services to forecast substantial deliverables. Fluent use of Java, Python, Salesforce, Zoho, Slack, Asana, Tableau, Visio, SQL, Microsoft Suite, ServiceNow and several other collaborative tools.

EXPERIENCE

Commercial Property Manager

09/2022 - Present

Haggard Property Group

Plano, TX

Property Manager with longstanding property management company specializing in commercial and residential properties.

- Saved \$7,000 on a property's triple net expenses by re-negotiating insurance rates & contractor's maintenance fees
- Was the sole point of contact for over 130+ properties managed by the agency
- Conducted more than 30 real estate closing
- Managed an average of 15 commercial and residential projects simultaneously
- Established and led agile analytics covering font, backend and testing activities for the products and services

Regional Operations Manager

10/2021 - 09/2022

Flyhomes Brokerage LLC

Dallas, TX

Regional manager supporting a team of 22 Realtors in Austin, Dallas-Fort Worth, and Houston implementing servant leadership for People Management and data science to achieve KPIs.

- Drive organizational results while also fostering a cohesive and collaborative team culture focused on mutual respect
- Oversaw the budget and schedule of a project to recruit, hire, and train 15 new employees at 3 locations
- · Analyze daily touring, scheduling, and purchasing trends for optimized staffing
- Ensure Texas Real Estate Commission guidelines are met, including; continuing education deadlines, intermediary standards, and brokerage service statements
- Achieved project milestones and deliverables with an internal team of 5 analysts

Operations and Client Services Manager

01/2019 - 10/2021

Skye Agency

Dallas, TX

Manage day to day operations for professional global staffing agency and provide end to end customer-focused support.

- Exceeded client satisfaction and productivity metrics above target for 5 consecutive quarters while managing multiple internal request
- Partner with clients to assess, create and implement best marketing practices for maintaining consumer loyalty
- Provide clients with an invoice estimate for services, interview and hire the onsite team, curate and provide training material for the team prior to execution
- Standardized touring efficacy and efficiency by creating multi-point checklist based on consumer feedback and closed client results
- Served as mentor to interns enrolled in SMU's International Business Program by providing guidance and training in agile method management and statistical analytic tools

EDUCATION

M.S., Adv Data Analytics

University of North Texas 2021 - 2023

B.A., Business Management

St. Martin's College

2006 - 2011

ACHIEVEMENTS

Standardized Property Tours

Flyhomes - Solidified companywide policy for consistent property tours for the 250+ Realtors in the US

Spearheaded Marketing Strategy

Flyhomes - Identified 20 grassroots events throughout Texas to partner with for company exposure; also managed and trained teams on consumer interactions

Stabilized and Increased Revenue

Skye Agency - Increased profits by 32% within st year by creating a matrix for accounts payable and receivable

Created and Implemented Cancellation Policy

Skye Agency - Wrote detailed policy for cancellations within 21, 14, and 7 days of an event

CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft SQL Server 2022 Essentials

February 2023

ServiceNow Fundamentals February 2023

Power BI Dataflows

February 2023

EXPERIENCE

National Experiential Product Specialist

2015 - 2018

2020 Companies

Dallas, TX

- Vendor for Samsung Telecommunications of North America

Train Field Sales Managers (FSMs) across the US on engaging with customers at consumer and client specific activations.

- Analyze, create, and implement best marketing practices for maintaining customer loyalty and relevance
- Underwrite and pitch local and national consumer engagement activities for the Samsung brand to participate in as either a vendor or sponsor
- Created engagement & leadership pamphlet to facilitate navigating from B2B sales to B2C sales
- Designed charts, graphs and reports on analytical findings for C-level leadership team

Marketing Analyst

2013 - 2016

JDA Technical Service Group

Irving, TX

- Vendor for Microsoft Corporation

Identify areas to improve productivity while reducing expenses associated with downtime.

- Served as lead analyst in consulting team, responsible for 2016 Budget with Variance analysis to prior years
- Reduced IPS (Customer Issues) by 2.2% while impacting nearly 3% of GMV
- · Created training manual for onboarding team members
- Routinely review and identify trends in performance level metrics based on benchmarks and quarterly KPIs

REFERENCES

Rusty Wooten, Skye Agency

Matthew Newman, 2020

972.800.0419

Companies 214.440.6717

Tim Bethea, Microsoft Inc

Audra Mills, ROI Group

214.725.2118

214.846.1246

CERTIFICATIONS

Tableau for Data Scientist February 2023

Excel for Accounting

December 2022

LinkedIn Leadership Mindsets Oct 2022

Texas Real Estate Agent Sept 2018

Social Media Marketing
September 2017

Six Sigma Green Belt May 2017

Project Management Professional April 2017

Project Management - Lean Process April 2017

Executive Management April 2017